so once you identified what it is you
want to do every day somebody said
counting their money in the last video I
think that's hilarious hey that's a
thing that's the thing maybe you just
want to count your money some people
want to be Filthy Rich and that's fine
just own it right just own what it is
that you want to do do you want to spend
all your all your days on a on a boat do
you want to be able to work do you want
to be able to take a month off do you do
you want to be able to you know work
remotely um can you not remot so we
already talked about the T activities we
just got rid of that video so the next
task is research which careers involve
those
activities and this one is harder right
because and this is where um all the
traditional like you know career
counseling comes in um you know it's it
requires a bunch of reading about what
the job is um there's another video that
we're going to talk about that talks
about um we're going to actually break
down the tech jobs um but I just wanted
to to Bullet point this video your your
task now is to figure out which careers
which jobs which things are who's going
to pay you to do those activities and
what are the names of those jobs what
are the titles associated with those
jobs that research is hard it's hard
because everybody says it differently
and I can't give you a specific answer
but that is the that is the now the
thing you need to do it's probably going
to take several hours for you to do this
it's only going to take a few minutes
for me to tell you you need to to do it
right but you've got to start
associating that that sheet of tasks
that you have that you want to do with
um you know the things that the jobs the
job descriptions for those things and um
you know it could be then some you can
kind of do it backwards too where you
can go just look at random jobs and talk
to a bunch of other people and say well
what do you do what how do you do it you
might not even know what is out there
right um if I had known that some of the
other careers EX existed I may not have
I may have taken a completely different
route Computer Engineering I really
actually enjoy Hardware but I didn't
have access to hardware and so I didn't
know to put emphasis on that when I was
you know doing the more serious learning
later on to get a job and thing um so
again research careers that in that have
those activities and get the titles and
um then that leads us to the next thing
where you're going to do the job